All right.
好的。
So we're getting close to the end of our lesson on technical descriptions technical English.
因此，我们的技术描述技术英语课程即将结束。
We're going to quickly talk about math or math equations.
我们将快速讨论数学或数学方程式。
Sometimes they're called equations.
有时它们被称为方程式。
Sometimes they're called problems.
有时它们被称为问题。
Math problems and we sometimes need to actually speak these out so let's just quickly go through this.
数学问题，我们有时需要真正说出这些问题，所以让我们快速完成。
Well if we're doing this one we're doing addition if we're doing this one we're doing subtraction.
好吧，如果我们正在做这个，我们正在做加法，如果我们正在做这个，我们正在做减法。
If we're doing this when we're doing division and if we're doing this when we're doing multiplication
如果我们在做除法时这样做，如果我们在做乘法时这样做
we are multiplying.
我们正在成倍增加。
If we're going to make these into verbs we're going to add seven and seven.
如果我们要将这些变成动词，我们将添加七和七。
We're going to subtract add it's the verb going to divide.
我们要减去 add 它是动词要除。
We're going to multiply and these words these verbs divide multiply subtract and add these words are
我们要乘，这些动词除以乘减和加这些词是
very common outside of math equations.
在数学方程之外非常常见。
So if you know these these words then you start to notice them spoken in lots of other situations.
因此，如果您知道这些词，那么您就会开始注意到它们在许多其他情况下所说的。
Well we should we should work hard so that we can multiply our success.
好吧，我们应该努力工作，这样我们才能成倍地取得成功。
We need to divide.
我们需要分开。
We need to divide the land divide the area.
我们需要划分土地划分区域。
Whatever.
任何。
OK could you please subtract my salary could you please subtract my salary.
好的，请您减去我的薪水，请您减去我的薪水。
I'd like you to add cucumbers.
我想让你加黄瓜。
I'd like you to add cucumbers or extra cheese.
我想让你加黄瓜或额外的奶酪。
So these verbs are very very common outside of math equations.
所以这些动词在数学方程式之外非常常见。
OK.
好的。
Just to be very clear when we're actually saying these math problems though we use the prepositions.
尽管我们使用了介词，但当我们实际上在说这些数学问题时要非常清楚。
So let's do it.
所以让我们去做吧。
Seven plus seven equals or is.
七加七等于或是。
So sometimes we say equals and sometimes we say is an either one is OK seven plus seven is 14.
所以有时我们说等于，有时我们说要么一就可以，七加七就是 14。
Seven plus seven equals 14.
七加七等于十四。
OK.
好的。
Seven minus seven equals zero seven minus seven is zero.
七减七等于零 七减七等于零。
Seven divided by seven divided by seven is one seven divided by seven is one equals one two divided
七除以七除以七是一七除以七一等于一二除
by.
经过。
Same Same thing different symbol divided by the forward slash here it's a special division symbol here
相同 相同的东西 不同的符号在这里除以正斜杠 这是一个特殊的除法符号
two divided by four equals zero point five equals zero point five OK seven times seven times seven is
二除以四等于零点​​五等于零点五确定七乘七乘以七是
forty nine seven times seven is forty nine.
四十九乘七等于四十九。
So we just need to be careful in knowing what we are doing OK.
所以我们只需要小心地知道我们在做什么。
These are less common what we can say if it's a verb which are very common words outside of math and
如果它是一个动词，这是数学之外非常常见的词，我们可以说这些不太常见，并且
what we should say if we're actually saying the math problem saying the equation plus minus divided
如果我们实际上是在说数学问题，说方程加减除，我们应该说什么
by at times.
有时。
Once you know those words though it's pretty easy and pretty simple and there's really nothing else
一旦你知道了这些词，虽然它很容易也很简单，而且真的没有别的了
to know.
要知道。
Of course if you get deeper into math there are lots more words and lots more things to describe.
当然，如果你对数学有更深的了解，就会有更多的词和更多的东西要描述。
But these are the basics and the most common words probably are these add subtract divide multiply.
但这些是基础知识，最常见的词可能是这些加减除乘。
These are the most common out there in the English language.
这些是英语中最常见的。